现在我们的第一个问题是电话屏幕问题
Now, we're at our first problem of
the day, the phone screen problem, so
我要点击这个链接，链接是可点击的，我要用这个链接。
I'm gonna click this link, the link is
clickable, and I'm using for this one.
我就像个采访者一样假装我是个采访者
And I'll pretend like I'm the interviewer,
like hey, blah, blah, blah.
我是 Jim Young ，我是 Netflix的高级软件工程师。
I'm Jim Young,
I'm a senior software engineer in Netflix.
我很感谢你今天花了时间来采访我
I really appreciate you taking
the time to interview with me today.
我知道我们都是忙碌的人没人喜欢采访
I know we're all busy people,
and no one likes interviewing.
所以我们会尽量让你开心
So we'll try to make
this pleasant possible.
请一分钟阅读这些问题，阅读需求，以及
Take a minute to read over the questions,
read of the requirements, and
让我知道你有什么问题
let me know if you have any questions.
那我就给他们一两分钟
Then I'll give them a minute or two.
我会说，好吧，如果你想要任何问题，我们走吧，开始吧。
I'll say, okay, if you want any questions,
let's go and get started.
请确保您的代码低于该行。
Make sure you code below the line.
在这里，确保遵循这些要求。
Here, and
make sure you follow the requirements.
不要导入任何库，仅以纯的香草 JavaScript 进行写入。
Don't import any libraries,
just write in pure, vanilla JavaScript.
而且你还有时间
And also, you have till some time.
所以现在，让我们继续处理这个问题。
So right now, let's go ahead and
tackle this problem.
很简单，这不是诡计，但这与问题相似
It's deceptively simple, it's not a trick,
but this is similar to questions
我确实会在一次真正的采访中给出，去解决这个问题，
that I would actually give during a real
interview, go and tackle this problem, and
看看你能拿到多远然后我们就能解决我的问题了
see how far you get, and then,
we'll go over what my solution was.
对于此问题，有多种解决方案。
And there are multiple
solutions to this problem.
还有一件事要问的是，你说，我可以用谷歌，或者 Bing，或者 Facebook，
And also, one thing to ask is, you said,
can I use Google, or Bing, or Facebook,
不管你怎么用脸书但是
whatever, when you use Facebook, but, yes,
你可以去找任何你想要的东西
you're allowed to look
up anything you want.
这是您在计算机上进行编码的过程中唯一的部分。
This is the only part of this course where
you'll be doing coding on your computer.
其他的我建议用一张纸来做
Everything else,
I recommend doing it on a piece of paper,
这才是你真正采访的方式
cuz that's how you do
it in a real interview.
在这方面，我正在寻找具体的产出。
For this part, I'm looking for
a specific output.